Contact

smcgruder@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/slovakia-mcgruder-0b568214 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Hospitals

Nursing

BLS

Certifications

Family Nurse Practitioner (FNP)
Certified Medical-Surgical
Registered Nurse (CMSRN)

Basic Life Support (BLS)

NRP

Honors-Awards

Nurse of the Year 2018

Slovakia McGruder

Family Nurse Practitioner

Dallas/Fort Worth Area

Summary

FNP actively seeking a full time or part time position!

For the last 20 years, I have worked with Med/Surg, Gynecological, Antepartum, Post Partum, Hospice, Home Health, Geriatric, Geriatric Psych, Dual Diagnosis Psych, Psych, long term care and rehab, and respite care patients.

In December 2018, I graduated with a post-master's in family nurse practitioner. I took and passed boards that same month. I became certified by the AANP in February 2019. Since then, I started working as an NP seeing patients in their home. Most recently, I started working part time in a primary care clinic.

Experience

Kelsom Clinic
Family Nurse Practitioner
October 2019 - Present (9 months)

My Home MD FNP-C July 2019 - Present (1 year) Mansfield, Texas

Providing primary care to clients in home

Texas Health Resources RN charge/ED navigator/Case Management/prenatal clinic September 2010 - August 2019 (9 years)

RN charge and prn ED navigator/CM

Travel max RN travel August 2009 - April 2010 (9 months)

Travel nurse at Dept. of Veterans Affairs-Dallas.

Page 1 of 2

Nurse Stat Agency

Lpn/Rn

October 2000 - August 2009 (8 years 11 months)

Supplemental staff in various facilities including hospitals, homes, nursing homes, and hospice.

Manhattan Health and Rehab

Lpn

October 1999 - December 2000 (1 year 3 months)

Charge and staff nurse

Education

Bradley University

Post Masters, Family Nurse Practitioner · (2016 - 2018)

Loyola University New Orleans

Master of Science in Nursing, Nursing Administration · (2012 - 2015)

William Carey University

Bachelor of Science (BS), Nursing · (2008 - 2009)

Holmes Community College

Associate of Arts and Sciences (AAS), ADN · (2006 - 2007)

Holmes Community College

Certificate, Practical Nursing · (1998 - 1999)